我是奥利弗·奎恩
My name is Oliver Queen.
五年里  我被困在地狱一般的小岛上
After five years on a hellish island,
我回来只有一个目标
I have come home with only one goal--
拯救我的城市
To save my city.
但要达到目标  我不能像过去一样成为凶手
But to do so, I can't be the killer I once was.
为了纪念我的朋友  我只能伪装成另一个人
To honor my friend's memory, I must be someone else.
深切怀念托马斯·梅林
孝子
成为另一个存在
I must be something else.
《绿箭》前情回顾
Previously on "Arrow"...
我在阿富汗的时候  我的部队的任务
When I was in Afghanistan,, my unit was tasked
是保护葛雷姆·卡迪尔
with protecting Gholem Qadir.
贩卖鸦片  贩卖儿童
Sold opium. Sold children.
你觉得你哥哥是怎么死的
How is it you think your brother ended up dead?
你向一名客户开枪  但是打偏了
You shot at a client, you missed.
我从不会打偏
I don't miss.
你杀了莎朵
You murdered Shado.
是的  扳机是我扣动的
Yes, I pulled the trigger,
但是你  枪口是你瞄准的
but you, you aimed the gun.
你在这里干什么
What are you doing here?
五年前  我对你做出过一项承诺
Five years ago, I made you a promise.
我不会让你死  直到你了解什么叫彻底绝望
You cannot die until you have known complete despair.
你会了解的  我向你承诺
And you will. I promise.
莎拉
Sara.
Sara?
凶手
Murderer.
[俄语]
你好吗  我的朋友
我能帮你什么
What can I do for you?
星城可没有古拉格监狱
There's no Gulags here in Starling City.
阿纳托利话太多
Anatoly talks too much.
是啊
Eto verno.
我需要你帮我找一个人
I need you to find a man for me.
他名叫斯莱德·威尔逊  是个有钱的澳大利亚人
His name is Slade Wilson. He's rich, Australian,
一只眼睛瞎了
and he's missing an eye.
我得知道他睡在哪里
I need to know where he sleeps.
首先  我需要你帮我的忙
First, I need your assistance with my business.
有个人欠我很大一笔钱
There is a man who owes me a substantial amount of money.
我不是来交易的
I am not here to trade.
你知道我们的友情是什么回事
You know how our brotherhood works.
我帮你一个忙
I do a favor for you
你也帮我一个忙
and you do one for me.
记在我账上  阿列克西
Put it on my tab, Aleksi.
我没时间玩这些游戏
I don't have time for these games.
那就腾出时间
Make time.
除非你对我有用
My services are of no use to you
否则我不对你提供帮助
unless yours are use to me.
好吧
Ok.
我知道这种友情是怎么回事
I know exactly how this brotherhood works,
现在  你为我服务
And right now, it works for me.
明白了吗
绿箭
第二季第十六集
我醒来时你已经走了
I woke up and you were gone.
我不累
Yeah. I wasn't tired.
你该累的
You should be.
你上次睡觉是什么时候
When's the last time you actually slept?
在我发现斯莱德·威尔逊还活着之前
Right before I found out that Slade Wilson is still alive.
你想谈谈吗
Do you want to talk?
我是说
I mean...
我知道我俩都
I know neither one of us
不大擅长分享感情
are very good about sharing our feelings,
但是我明白
but...I mean, I get it.
斯莱德  还有...
Slade, and...
事情很多
And it's a lot, and, you know,
如果你害怕也没关系  我也是
it's ok if you're scared. I am, too.
我不怕
I'm not scared.
斯莱德回星城是有计划的
Slade came back to Starling City with an agenda.
首先  他想大量生产米拉库鲁
First, he tries to mass produce the Mirakuru.
然后他出现在
Then he shows up...
我母亲的家里
at my mother's house.
他想争斗  没问题
So he wants a fight, fine.
我满足他  这次
I'll give him a fight. And this time,
我杀了他时
when I kill him,
会保证他死得透透的
I will make damn sure that he stays dead.
我只是得找到他
I just need to find him.
咖啡吗
Coffee?
热可可
Hot cocoa.
没有棉花糖吗
What, no marshmallows?
没有了
I'm out.
你在这里做什么  狄格
What are you doing here, Dig?
留神一切
Keeping an eye on things.
好吧  你说的一切指的是我的脖子吧
Ok. And by things, you mean my neck.
你觉得斯莱德·威尔逊会趁我睡着时扭断它
The one you think Slade Wilson's going to break in my sleep.
是啊  类似吧
Yeah, something like that.
我派遣了额外保安保护奥利弗的妈妈
Look, I have extra security details on Oliver's mother.
罗伊照看着西娅
Roy's keeping an eye on Thea,
莎拉和劳蕾尔在一起
Sara's staying close to Laurel.
所以我摊上了你  坐在我家门外
So I get you sitting outside of my house
就像大一那个曲棍球队员一样
like that lacrosse player my freshman year of college.
在遇见你和奥利弗之前  我有生活的
You know, I had a life before you and oliver, yeah?
好吧  我只想确保你没事  费利西蒂
Right. I just want to make sure you're ok, Felicity.
我很喜欢你这样
And I love you for it.
但如果斯莱德想杀了我  他就能做到
But if Slade wants to kill me, he can.
你无法阻止他
There's nothing you can do to stop him.
回家去  好吗
So go home. Ok?
睡衣蛮好看
Nice jammies.
奥斯特兰德酒店
1141房间  马上来
怎么这么久才来
What took you so long?
这是搞什么
What is all this?
现在喝香槟有点早  不是吗
A little early for champagne, don't you think?
我不觉得
Not for me.
我刚从平壤执行完任务
I just got back from a mission in Pyongyang.
该死
Well, damn.
是你啊
That was you?
对不起  那是机密信息
I'm sorry. That's classified information.
但我想念我的前夫  新男友
But I missed my ex-husband, new boyfriend.
超能联合调查组在这个酒店
And A.R.G.U.S. has a standing reservation
给重要人物留了一个长久房
at this hotel for very important assets.
你能留下来吗
Can you stay?
奥利弗和我遇上了...
Well, Oliver and I kind of have a...
一点事
situation.
一切都没事吧
Everything all right?
是啊  我们在处理
Yeah, yeah, we're handling it.
就是说能留下来
So you can stay.
阿富汗  坎大哈  南区指挥部
有什么问题吗  麦考斯
Is there a problem, Michaels?
六年前
我们需要休息  女人们都累了
We need to rest. These women are tired.
我们都累了
We're all tired.
距离营地还有很长的路  继续走
It's a long hike back to camp. Keep going.
要我去向女人们解释
Shall I go explain to the
需要在天黑前回去的原因吗
ladies why they want to get back before dark?
她们不能和你说话
They're not allowed to talk to you.
为什么  因为我是个美国人吗
Why, 'cause I'm an American?
因为你是个男人
Because you're a man.
休息五分钟吧
Five minutes.
女人参军  不能挺
Girls in the military. Can't keep up,
就别进  这话真没错
don't join up, right?
你还好吗
喝不喝水
我的脚出问题了
给你
我有件事需要告诉你
[普什图语]
怎么了
Whoa, whoa, hey, what's going on here?
怎么回事
What's going on?
你认出来了吗
You recognize that face?
你应该认识
You should.
他在美军高价值目标名单上
He's on the U.S. Military's high value target list.
葛雷姆·卡迪尔
Gholem Qadir.
贩卖鸦片的大毒枭兼军火商
Opium drug lord and arms dealer.
务必活捉
Wanted alive.
你之前说参军的女人怎么着来着
What were you saying about women in the military?
我们结婚的时候为什么没做这些有趣的事
Why didn't we do fun stuff like this when we were married?
从我们繁忙的日程中
And take time out from our
抽出时间把另一半搞疯吗
busy schedule of driving each other crazy?
阿曼达
Amanda.
别一副担心的样子  麦考斯探员
Don't look so worried, Agent Michaels.
我们都会在职业生涯的某个时间点
We've all availed ourselves
利用自己的身份来获取一些利益
of the ostrander suite at some point in our careers.
发生了一些事  跟我一起走一趟吧
Something's come up, I'll need you to come with me.
工作来了
Duty calls.
我猜也是
Yeah, guess so.
其实
Actually...
我是指你们两个
I meant both of you.
我们正在看的这个是什么
What are we looking at here?
羟基环沙林  一种神经毒素
Hydroxy-cyclosarin. It's a nerve agent.
是一种化学武器的原型
It's the apocalypse in the form of a chemical weapon.
准备用于袭击一处自由市场
And it's about to hit the open market.
是超能力联合调查组的探员们
A.R.G.U.S. agents uncovered
在坎达格的一座制造工厂里发现的
a manufacturing plant in Kahndaq.
几乎所有样本都已记录在案  除了一个
All samples were accounted for, except for one.
这段录像在两周之后拍摄于
Two weeks later, this footage
库拉克南部的一个偏僻村庄
was captured in a remote village in southern Qurac.
一毫升就能杀死方圆十英里内的生物
One milliliter has a kill radius of ten miles.
而那些样品只需要一半就能达到同等效果
It only took half that amount to produce these results.
我们的线人追踪到样本
Our sources have traced the
穿越欧洲送到了马尔科维亚的一处地方
sample through Europe to an estate in Markovia.
那就派军队去吧
So send in the army.
如果派军队  我们的政府就要面对
We send in the army, we risk an international spectacle
无法承受的国际压力
our government can't afford.
这件事必须秘密处理
This has to be off-book.
如果你需要我起草强夺方案  没问题
If you need me to draw up the smash and grab, done.
但约翰不是外勤探员  他没有资格
But John isn't a field agent. He's not qualified.
就他和奥利弗·奎恩
Judging from how he and Oliver Queen
在业余时间里做的事而言
spend their free time,
我说他很够格
I'd say his credits transfer.
听着  我比你更不想
Hey, look, I don't want this
看到这件事被曝光
thing out in the open any more than you do,
但我可不会让
but I'm not sending my
我老板再陪着你来趟商务旅行
boss in on another one of your business trips.
这件事我不打算扯上绿箭侠
I have no intention of involving the Arrow.
我需要你
I need you.
为什么
What for?
葛雷姆·卡迪尔
Gholem Qadir.
我们抓到过他
We caught him.
国防部几年前把卡迪尔放了
D.O.D. turned Qadir loose a few years ago.
谁想出来的好主意
Who thought that was a good idea?
这个世界很复杂  约翰尼
It's a complicated world, Johnny.
那个神经毒素不是卡迪尔
The nerve agent's not the only WMD
唯一想经手的大规模杀伤性武器
Qadir's tried getting his scummy fingers on.
上个月  他想购买马尔科姆·梅林的
Last month, he tried to buy Malcolm Merlyn's
地震机原型
prototype earthquake machine.
顺便说一下  谢谢你阻止了他
Thank you for stopping that, by the way.
幸运的是  他不知道你也参与了那件事
Fortunately, he doesn't know about your involvement in that.
他只记得你救过他的性命
He remembers you as the man who tried to save his life.
神经毒素被锁住了  钥匙在
The nerve agent's under lock and key
他在马尔科维亚的那处房产里
at his estate in Markovia.
日程表显示近期那里会举办一场募捐活动
He's scheduled to host a fundraiser there shortly.
我们两个人几乎不怎么联系
The two of us haven't exactly kept in touch.
这个我们来搞定  但是时机稍纵即逝
We've got that covered, but our window is rapidly closing.
好吧
OK.
那我去潜入募捐场地  把东西带出来
So I infiltrate the fundraiser, come out with the package.
听起来挺简单的
Sounds simple enough.
我们这行没什么是简单的
Nothing in this business is simple.
你知道的  狄格尔先生
You know that, Mr. Diggle.
跟我来
Follow me.
我不需要你的帮助就能把毒剂带出来
I don't need you to get the nerve agent out.
我需要你把你的队伍带进去
I need you to get your team in.
我的队伍
My team?
他们被称作X特遣部队
They're designated "Task Force X."
饶了我吧
Give me a break.
没什么特遣部队
This ain't no task force.
还是这么说吧
Let's call it like it is--
欢迎加入自杀小队
Welcome to the suicide squad.
不只是在残酷体罚中成长
"It's not only prisoners who grow course and hardened
并变得坚强的囚徒  还有那些
"from corporal punishment, but those as well
犯下罪行和拒绝作证的人
who perpetrate the act or who are present to witness it."
别跟他说书了
Oh, please stop giving him books.
这就是你的作战队伍吗  沃勒
So this is your unit, huh, Waller?
OJ和查尔斯·曼森有事不能来了吗
What, OJ and Charles Manson weren't available?
O·J·辛普森  斩首谋杀其妻及一男招待
查尔斯·曼森  残杀导演波兰斯基孕妻及朋友
这是一次危险的行动
This is a dangerous operation.
这些人都具备很有用的技能
And these men have useful skills.
任务应该有所妥协
Should the mission be compromised...
你写下来吧
You'll just write them off.
自杀小队
The suicide squad.
就跟他会做出牺牲似的
Yeah, like he would ever make the sacrifice.
莱拉  我不敢相信你也有份
Lyla, I can't believe you're on board with this.
那些人是杀人犯
Those men are murderers!
那奥利弗·奎恩和莎拉·兰斯
And what's the number of bodies
又杀了多少人
between Oliver Queen and Sara Lance?
他们做的事和我做的事  完全不同
What they do, what I do, is completely different.
并不尽然  约翰  你还不明白吗
Not really, John. Don't you see that?
我明白的是你让杀了我哥哥的家伙
What I see is you letting the man who killed my brother
逍遥法外
roam completely free.
不是给他自由  这是工作
It's not freedom. It's work.
这是错误的
It's wrong.
你们这些小可爱需要建议吗
Do you cuties need some counseling?
我可是专业的治疗师
I'm a trained therapist.
威登酒吧
"你有销售经验吗"
"Do you have previous experience in retail?"
购物算吗
Does shopping count?
莎拉
Sara?
我见过这幅表情
I've seen that look before.
当奥利进入生人勿进模式时  我在镜子中的表情
On my face in the mirror when Ollie goes into distant mode.
坚持下去
Hang in there.
当他准备好时  会向你敞开心扉的
He'll open up to you when he's ready.
是啊  你说得没错
Yeah. You'd think so.
我从追踪威尔逊先生
I started by tracing the donation
在莫伊拉竞选中的捐款开始
Mr. Wilson made to Moira's campaign.
所有捐款
All of the money was
都经过了一系列的海外账户
routed through a series of offshore accounts.
没有一个与本地相关联
None of which link back to a local address,
所以我查了信用卡交易记录
so I looked into credit card transactions
-还有汽车租赁协议  -什么
- and car rental agreements. - What?
他肯定会以某种方式四处躲藏  但不会租汽车
He's got to get around somehow, just not by rental car.
斯莱德以前是情报科学学会的
Slade's former ASIS.
他知道如何隐藏行踪
He knows how to be a ghost.
发生抢劫事件
Robbery in progress.
在第五大街和吉芬街处
5th and Giffen.
我们还打击犯罪  是吧
We're still in the crime fighting business, right?
马尔科维亚  马尔科夫堡
艺术品拍卖会
先驱者已盯紧目标
Harbinger has eyes on the target.
点燃火把
Light the torches.
死亡射手准备就绪
Deadshot is a go.
榴散弹准备就绪
Shrapnel's a go.
老虎准备就绪
Tiger's a go.
我是知更鸟
This is Mockingbird.
先驱者  你可以随时行动
Harbinger, you have a green light.
自由枪骑兵准备就绪了  死亡射手呢
Freelancer, you're a go. Deadshot?
自由枪骑兵在我视野中
Got Freelancer in my sights.
为什么不朝我开枪
What's stopping you from shooting me right now?
乐意之极
Honor.
麻烦给支香烟行吗  我的朋友
Can I trouble you for a cigarette, my friend?
我不抽烟  而且我也不是你朋友
I don't smoke, and I'm not your friend.
你知道我是谁吗
You know who I am?
我是做什么的吗
What it is I do?
你贩卖毒品  军火  儿童
You're dealing drugs, weapons and children.
在战争中左右逢源
Play both sides of the conflict.
你的祖国深陷战火  你还在捞钱
Make money while your country burns.
这样的人可不止我一个
I do not have to be the only one.
放了我  我给你荣华富贵
Let me go, I make you rich.
想收买我的人吗  卡迪尔
You trying to bribe my men, Qadir?
如果我们想赚钱
If we wanted to make a buck,
就不会来这个地方  白痴
this is the last place we'd be, moron.
趴下
Get down!
对不起  我没有看到...
Sorry, I wasn't looking where I was--
葛雷姆·卡迪尔
Gholem Qadir.
真是不敢相信
I do know what is less likely--
约翰·狄格尔会这么笨拙
that John Diggle would be clumsy,
世界这么大竟然在这里遇到你
or I would find him here, of all places.
你喜欢艺术吗  我的朋友
You like art, my friend?
我善于抓住好的投资机会
I know a good investment when I see one.
那你是退伍了吗
Out of the military, then?
还干了个比较赚钱的行当
And in a more lucrative line of work.
你干的是什么行当呢
What kind of work is that?
一个你不应该问的行当
The kind you don't get to ask about.
很高兴见到你  葛雷姆
It's good seeing you, Gholem.
一切正常吗  狄格尔先生
Everything all right here, Mr. Diggle?
是的  他跟我一起的
Yes, he's with me.
你这个士兵现在还有护卫了
So the soldier now has his own security.
在这个行业中  若做得好  就会得罪人
In my line of work, when I do a good job, I tend to make enemies.
好人变成坏人
A good man turns bad.
坏人变成好人
Bad man turns good.
你改变了我的人生
You changed my life, you know.
相信我  那不是我本意
Trust me, that was never my intention.
我给你们的政府提供了情报
The intelligence I provided your government,
保住了我的命
it saved many lives.
现在我自由了  我会尽力做出回报
Now as a free man, I give back when I can.
当然
Of course.
趴下
Get down!
没事了
It's all clear.
似曾相识啊  朋友
Deja vu, my friend.
卡迪尔先生
Mr. Qadir!
我没事
I am fine.
我肯定不是目标
I do not believe I was the target.
正如我所说  当我干得好时  就会得罪人
Like I said, when I do my job right, I tend to make enemies.
我们得走了
We should go.
干得好  死亡射手  准备离开现场
Good job, Deadshot. You're a go for exfil.
正在离开
Already in motion.
但是
Except, uh,
不止我一个人
I'm not the only one.
榴散弹刚刚跑了
Shrapnel just bolted.
找到他
Find him.
正在跟踪他  往东去了
Picking him up, headed east.
榴散弹
Shrapnel.
停下  返回集结点
Stand down and return to the rally point.
我不会加入你们高尚的军队
I won't be conscripted into your moral army.
停下  最后警告
Stand down! Final warning.
特别是在一个没有引渡条约的国家
Especially not while in a country without an extradition treaty.
很好
Very well.
怎么回事
What the hell's going on?
榴散弹刚刚被罚出场了
Shrapnel just fouled out of the game.
刚才怎么回事
What the hell was that?
我们正准备为此吃爆米花庆祝呢
We're going to want popcorn for this.
约翰  你自己也说过  他们是杀人犯
You said it yourself, John. They're murderers.
是罪犯
Criminals.
他们需要激励来听从命令
They need an incentive to follow orders.
那你就把炸药装进他的头里吗
So you rigged their heads with explosives?
只要他们守规矩就没有危险
There's no danger as long as they play by the rules.
谢费尔不守规矩
Scheffer didn't.
我好像都不认识你了  莱拉
It's like I don't even know you anymore, Lyla.
卡迪尔的事现在什么情况
Where are we at with Qadir?
救人一命  得到一枚银星勋章
Save a man's life once, get a silver star.
救人两命  租件晚礼服吧
Save it twice? Rent a tux.
等待您的下一步指示  长官
I'll await further instructions, sir.
葛雷姆
请光临我的人道主义募捐会  已附详情与说明
你的人可真难搞啊
我的耐性也不多
So is my patience.
这是你那位威尔逊先生的星城银行账号
This is Starling City Bank account number for your Mr. Wilson.
先说好
To be clear...
你拿走信封后我们就两清了
take this envelope and we are through.
我对你的朋友没兴趣
I do not care who your friends are.
能达成共识吗
别紧张  是我
Relax, it's just me.
你怎么了  奥利
What's going on, Ollie?
你可以和我谈谈
Hey! Talk to me.
现在还不到时候
Now is not the time.
那要等到什么时候
Then when is the time?
为什么要找黑手党  你失控了
The Bratva, Ollie? You're losing your grip.
斯莱德影响了你的判断
Ok? Slade's getting in your head.
我想结束这一切
I need this to stop.
所以  我得找到他
And for it to stop, I need to find him.
在那之前  你觉得你
Yeah, and until then, how long do you think
一个人可以撑多久
you can keep this up for?
你不吃东西  很少休息
You're not eating, you're barely sleeping.
只要睡下就会做噩梦
And when you do, you have nightmares.
你梦到她了  是不是
They're about her, aren't they?
看着我
Hey, look at me.
你已经尽力了
You did what you had to do, ok?
艾沃当时差点杀死了我们两个
Ivo was going to shoot Shado, or me, or both of us.
那是不可能的选择
It was an impossible choice.
但我选了
I made it, anyway.
但如果你没那么选
But if you had chosen differently,
那你每晚梦到的将会是我
then it would be me haunting you at night.
你现在也有危险  莎拉
It still could be, Sara.
所以我们得分开
That's why we have to stop.
你什么意思
What are you saying?
他会利用你伤害我
He's going to use you to hurt me.
或直接攻击你
Or he's going to hurt you...
跟我保持距离
Stay away from me.
既然你还没有提起
Seeing as how you haven't brought it up,
据我分析  我给你的线索里
I'm guessing you haven't got very far
你并没有查到什么
with that H.I.V.E. Lead I gave you.
少废话  做你的事
Just make this quick.
你还是这么健谈  约翰
You're usually so chatty, John.
是女人的问题吗  她骗到你了吗
These problems with your girl, they got you down, huh?
那你的女儿呢
And what about your girl?
你在牢里供起来的那个
The one you have a shrine to in that cell of yours?
佐伊
Zoe.
你女儿知道你是做什么的吗
Does your daughter know what you do for a living?
她就是我做这行的原因
She is why I do what I do.
-真的吗  -对
- Really? - Yeah.
一个小女孩能有多少敌人
How many enemies can a little girl have?
我不知道
I wouldn't know.
我花不掉的酬劳
Everything I make beyond expenses
都汇进了一个保密信托
goes in a blind trust.
女孩最想要的是爸爸
A girl needs her father.
不会是我这个爸爸
Nah, not this father.
我唯一能为她做的
Best thing I can do for her life...
就是不参与她的人生
not be in it.
好了吗
Is it ready?
我们花了好大力气才给约翰
You know, we went through all that trouble to get Johnny here
搞到这个破舞会的邀请函
invited to this little shindig.
不用就太可惜了
Seems like an awful waste not to use that invitation.
你来用  一旦神经药剂得手
You're using it. Once you have hands on the nerve agent,
就放进口袋走人
pocket it, walk right on out.
遵命
Copy that.
非常感谢您的倾情赞助
Thank you very much. Your generosity is much appreciated.
虽然这身不是迷彩服
That's not exactly army camo.
可你想过万一卡迪尔认出你该怎么办吗
But have you given any thought to what would happen if Qadir recognizes you anyway?
狄格先生  这是哪位美人啊
Mr. Diggle. Who is this vision?
他的新保镖
His new bodyguard.
那你可得给我介绍下你的保安公司了
Mmm. You will have to refer me to your security company.
很高兴你今晚能前来
I'm glad you could come tonight.
这远不足以报答你对我的两次
It's the least I could do after you saved my life.
救命之恩
Again.
我们里面见  伙计
I will see you inside, my friend.
葛雷姆
Gholem.
我似乎没来得及
It would seem I didn't have time
帮我的保镖办理邀请函
to get credentials for my associate.
来  跟我一起
Come. This way.
我很抱歉
Gosh, I'm so sorry.
我忘记还有这个了
I forgot those were in there.
尽情享受  狄格先生
Enjoy the benefit, Mr. Diggle.
死亡射手和装备都到位了
Deadshot and his gear are in position.
老虎总揽全局
Tiger's got the overwatch.
全体注意  准备行动
Harbinger to all, fire in the hole.
十点钟方向有敌人
Shooter at my ten!
我掩护你
I got you covered!
好  快上
Bounding! Go go go!
全歼
All clear!
还是个孩子
It's just a kid.
你今晚真漂亮
And don't you look lovely tonight?
谢谢
Appreciate it.
我觉得你应该和你的保镖跳支舞
Oh, I think you owe your bodyguard a dance.
请吧
I insist.
死亡射手正在前去取包裹
Deadshot en route to package.
世界的命运
The fate of the world
落在弗洛伊德·罗通手上
resting in the hands of Floyd Lawton.
这有利于任务
It helps to focus on the mission.
你就是这么麻痹自己的吗
Is that what you tell yourself?
我不会以扭曲的眼光
I tell myself to see the world how it is,
看待这个世界
not how I want to see it.
我们都行走在灰色地带
We both operate in the grey.
唯一的差别就是  我愿意承认
The only difference is, is I'm willing to admit it.
那不是我们两个唯一的差别
That's not the only difference between us.
你说得对  但我不喜欢评判别人
That's true. I don't judge other people for it.
莱拉  我还是原来的那个我
Lyla, I'm the same man I've always been.
我也没有变啊
And I'm who I've always been.
你太固执了  约翰
You're rigid, John.
你不接受任何其他人的看法
You're blind to any viewpoint that isn't yours.
过去的几个月很开心
These past few months have been amazing.
但我们一直沉溺玩乐  而非交流
But we've done more playing than talking.
因为我们一旦开始谈  就会闹分手
Because when we talk, we tend to get divorced.
威登酒吧
别担心
Don't worry.
这是我第一次做
It's virgin.
所以它尝起来才那么糟吗
Ugh. Which is why it tastes terrible.
是啊
True.
所以
So.
看来你和莎拉进展不错
It looks like things with you and Sara are going well.
我觉得这个话题不该和你谈
I'm not sure you're the best person to talk to with all this.
为什么
And why is that?
是因为出轨  沉船  溺水
Is it because of the whole cheating, shipwreck, drowning,
没淹死  你回来了  她也回来了这事吗
not drowning, you're back, she's back thing?
抱歉
Sorry.
我说得很残忍但也很诚实
It's brutal AA honesty talking.
我想我更喜欢我们相互欺骗的时候
I think I preferred it when we were all lying to each other.
不  你只是觉得你喜欢
No, you just thought you did.
我几乎比所有人都了解你  奥利
I know you better than almost anyone, Ollie.
我知道你觉得自己不配得到幸福
I know that you think that you don't deserve to be happy,
但你错了
but you're wrong.
你或许认为跟她保持一定距离
You may think that keeping her at arm's length,
是在保护她  但其实并不是
you're protecting her, but you're not.
你只是在保护自己
You're only protecting yourself.
不是那么简单
It's more complicated than that.
从来都不简单
It always is.
我查到你给我的那银行账户的地址了
I got the address for that account number you gave me.
我来叫罗伊和莎拉
I'll call Roy and Sara.
不  我不会让斯莱德有更多目标
No. I'm not giving Slade any more targets.
你不能只身前往  那是自杀
You can't go out there by yourself, it's suicide.
这事由我们两人而起
This started with the two of us.
也要结束于我们两人之间
That's how it ends.
死亡射手已就位
Deadshot's on target.
找到了
Bingo.
我不知道该怎么办
I don't know what to do.
他领先太多了
He's too far ahead.
他花了好多年计划这一切
I mean, he spent years planning this,
而且他知道有关我的一切
and he knows everything about me.
我不能  我...
I can't, I...
我不知道怎么阻止他
I don't know how to stop him.
你可以让别人帮你
Well, you start by letting people help you.
但他会来对付你的
But he's going to come after you.
你之所以活着...
You're alive...
是因为莎朵死了
because Shado isn't.
等他来的时候  你觉得我们俩在不在一起
And when he does, do you think it'll make a difference
会有区别吗
whether or not we're together?
让他来吧
Let him come.
我不再是他在岛上认识的那个小女孩了
I'm not the girl he knew on the island.
我没那么容易被杀死的
I'm not that easy to kill.
一起面对
Together?
Together.
我进来了
I'm in.
30秒后神经毒剂到手
I'll have the nerve agent in my pocket in 30 seconds.
先驱者
Harbinger...
我这里出了一点小状况
We've got what I would describe as a little bit of a situation here.
解释清楚
Explain.
我看到神经毒剂了
Well, I got eyes on the nerve agent,
但我无法移动它
and I'm not going to be able to move it,
更不用直接拿走了
much less pocket it.
原地待命  死亡射手  我要跟沃勒汇报一下
Stand by, Deadshot. I need to talk to Waller.
知更鸟  请说
Go for Mockingbird.
我们遇到麻烦了
We have a situation.
目标比行动前指示的大很多
The package is much bigger than our pre-op briefing indicated.
原地待命
Stand by.
死亡射手已就位  我需要看到他所看到的
Deadshot's on target; I need to see what he does.
激活他眼里的摄像头
Activate the camera in his eye piece.
罗通装备的多光谱视频
Multi spectrum from Lawton's rig
马上出现
coming in...now.
相符
It's a match.
老虎  准备撤退
Tiger, move for extraction.
死亡射手  原地不动
Deadshot, remain in position.
先驱者和自由枪骑兵  撤退到集合点
Harbinger and Freelancer, evac and head to the rally point.
死亡射手还没有带着东西上来
Deadshot still isn't topside with the package.
我只是需要看到罢了  撤到集合点
I only needed eyes on. Fall back to the rally point.
等等  你早知道神经毒剂太大不能带走吗
Wait...you knew that the nerve agent was too large to be extracted?
撤退到集合点
Fall back to the rally point.
九号已准备好
Nine is inbound and hot.
知更鸟撤出
Mockingbird out.
九号是什么
What the hell are Nines?
MQ九号  劫掠者
Mq-9s. Predators.
沃勒发动了无人机袭击
Waller's called in a drone strike.
十分钟之内  这里的所有人都会死
Everyone here is dead inside of ten minutes.
九号装载着地狱火导弹
The Nines carry the hellfire missile.
只要一枚就足以把这栋大楼夷为平地
Just one of them can level this whole building.
你老板不在乎会把谁炸死
And your boss doesn't care who's here when it does.
莱拉  我们得把这些人弄出去
Lyla, we have to get these people out of here.
或许我们可以激活房屋警报
Maybe there's a house alarm we can trigger.
约翰  我们必须要走了
John, we have to move now.
我有个更好的主意
I have a better idea.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
请大家注意
Can I have your attention, please?
感谢我们的主办人
In honor of our host.
葛雷姆·卡迪尔擅长做一切他决心要做的事
Gholem Qadir excels at everything he puts his mind to,
生意
be it business,
慈善
philanthropy...
或者恐怖主义事业
or terrorism.
我觉得葛雷姆是一个文艺复兴式的人物
Yeah, I guess you could say gholem is somewhat of a renaissance man.
他在每个领域都涉足一点
He dabbles in a little bit of everything.
比如说军火交易  我说性交易了吗
Like arms trading-- did I mention the sex trafficking?
还有他手里的致命神经毒剂
Or the deadly nerve agent that he's holding
就在这舞池下面10米的地方
just 30 feet beneath this very dance floor.
这都是谎话  这个人是雇佣兵
These are lies! This man is a mercenary!
劳顿
Lawton!
他没有回答  我得去帮他
He's not answering. I have to go help him.
我真不敢相信我刚说了这些
I can't believe I just said that.
你  你五年前也在阿富汗
You! You were in Afghanistan five years ago.
你和那个叛徒从一开始就在骗我
You and that Judas have been deceiving me from the start.
来得正好
Good timing.
我的邀请涵迟迟不来  等烦了
Got tired of waiting for my invitation.
违抗命令了啊  约翰
Disobeying orders, John.
小心身后
Behind you.
你欠我两个人情了
That's two you owe me, junior.
我们得走了
We have to go.
沃勒让我待在这里
Waller told me to stay here.
无人机马上就会来袭了
There's an incoming drone strike.
真及时  让你的队员都出去
How contemporary. Get your team clear.
你就是我的队员之一
You are on my team.
你该离开了
And it's time for you to go.
是啊  说得对  是时候了
Yeah, that's right. It is time.
这就是我离开的方式
And this is my way to go.
自杀小队  记得吗
Suicide squad, remember?
我可有可无  约翰
I'm expendable, John.
我脑中那颗该死的炸弹也能证明这一点
Even got the damn bomb in my head to prove it.
这样  我至少做了件光荣的事
This way, at least I get to go out doing something honorable.
你不能死得这么容易  罗通
You don't get to die that easy, Lawton.
是吗
Really?
那你给我一个
Why don't you give me even just
不这么做的理由
one good reason why not, huh?
佐伊
Zoe.
-那神经毒气怎么办  -相信我
- What about the nerve gas? - Believe me--
沃勒已经都搞定了
Waller's already got that covered.
快走  快快快
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
无人机改变飞行路线了  现在正跟着我们
The drone shifted course. It's following us.
你觉得很好笑吗
Do you find that funny?
那个女人真厉害啊
Whoa. What a woman.
你们觉得她是怎么知道把无人机派去哪里的
How do you think she knew where to send the drone, huh?
我是说确切的坐标地点
And I mean, the precise coordinates.
-移植追踪器  -炸弹和GPS
- The implants. - Bomb and GPS.
很聪明对吧
Pretty clever, right?
无人机的目标不是葛雷姆的房子
The drone ain't targeting Gholem's house.
而是我
It's targeting me.
等等  不该先问问我的意见吗
Whoa, hang on, do I get a say in this?
-转身  -你干什么
- Turn around. - What are you doing?
我宁愿被炸飞
Look, I think I'd rather get blown up!
稳住  会很疼的
Hold still. This is going to hurt.
马尔科夫政府威胁说要报复
The Markovian government is threatening retaliation
在禁飞区无缘无故出动无人机袭击
following an unprovoked drone attack over a no-fly zone.
我们不就是想避免这种局面吗  做得漂亮啊
Just the attention we wanted to avoid. Well done.
又不是我派无人机去的
I'm not the one who sent that drone.
无人机隐身了  化学武器藏匿点
It was cloaked. An explosion atop
上面的爆炸是很容易解释的
a chemical weapons cache is easy to explain.
可是  还有目击者  所以我们
Instead, there were witnesses and we had
还得派海豹突击队去清理现场
to send in a seal team to clean out the estate.
我觉得你拉我帮你干什么不干净的勾当时
I guess you'll think twice before dragging me
就应该三思而后行  沃勒
in to do your dirty work, Waller.
我并不觉得这是个问题
Somehow I don't think it will be an issue.
就这样  狄格尔先生
Good day, Mr. Diggle.
不可思议啊
Kind of uncanny.
狄格尔怎么知道罗通的追踪器在什么地方
How Diggle knew exactly where Lawton's implant was.
总之
Still,
这暴露出了一个明显的设计缺陷
it exposed an obvious design flaw.
以后把追踪器植入到脊椎里吧
We'll be putting in the implants in their spinal vertebrae now.
让罗通跟其他人准备手术
Have Lawton and the others prepped for surgery.
沃勒说几年后你可能会得到赦免
Waller said in a few years, you might even get a pardon.
不用担心  约翰
Don't worry, John.
我不会活那么久的  你我心知肚明
We both know I'm not going to be around that long.
没被解雇吗
You still employed?
我这种权限级别的人没那么容易
People with my security clearance aren't that easy
-就摆脱的  -对
- to get rid of. - Right.
那我们呢  约翰
What about us, Johnny?
昨晚杀我弟弟的那个人
Last night, the man who killed my brother
比要保护全世界的那个女人
showed more character than the woman charged
更加高尚
with protecting the world.
是非好坏的界限已经没那么明显了
Good and bad is not so clear to me.
但是有一件事我非常确定
One thing I do know for sure,
黑白分明那么确定
black and white...
就是我不能再失去你了
is that I can't ever lose you again.
终于
Finally.
我们也达成一致了
Something we agree on.
又多了一个原先是恐怖分子的盟友
Well, there goes another terrorist-turned-ally.
对了  我推荐你
By the way, I put you in for a commendation
去救卡迪尔了
for saving Qadir's ass.
记得请我喝酒
You owe me a beer.
恭喜
Congratulations.
是啊  杀个孩子得到勋章  对吧
Yeah, well, kill a kid, get a medal, right?
要是那个人拿卡拉希步枪朝你射击
When someone's shooting a kalishnikov at you,
那他就不是个孩子
he's not a kid.
我不这么认为
I see things differently.
世界很复杂  约翰
It's a complicated world, Johnny.
我可以叫你约翰吗
Is it OK if I call you Johnny?
我好像还不知道你的名字  麦考斯
I don't think I caught your first name, Michaels.
莱拉
Lyla.
真的很高兴认识你  莱拉
It's really good to meet you, Lyla.
下面是国际新闻  一支联合国巡查队
In international news, a United Nations inspections team
因为藏在人道主义者葛雷姆·卡迪尔
was called to a chemical weapons manufacturing facility
马尔科夫庄园下的
hidden beneath the Markovian estate
化学武器生产制造设施而出动
of humanitarian Gholem Qadir.
星城新闻  市长候选人莫伊拉·奎恩
Closer to home, mayoral candidate Moira Queen
在各地进行演说
stumped for an initiative
企图在学校游泳池建造项目后再复兴市中心
to revive inner city after school swim programs.
我记得自己的孩子小时候
Oh, I remember how much my children
有多么喜欢游泳
enjoyed swimming when they were young.
他们在泳池里拉都拉不出来
I couldn't get them out of the pool.
我们需要...
We need--
我还以为你不喜欢游泳
I thought you hated swimming.
我恨游泳
I detest swimming.
西娅也是
So does Thea.
有时候我母亲
My mother sometimes--ahem--
不是那么喜欢真相
enjoys a casual relationship with the truth.
总之
Anyway.
谢谢你在这里陪我
Thank you for being there for me.
你是说不让你把我推开吗
You mean for not letting you push me away?
我不会再那样了
I'm going to stop doing that.
是吗  那就好
Yeah? Good.
反正你也是在浪费自己的时间
You'll be wasting your time, anyways.
好像你听从我的建议了
It looks like you took my advice.
谢谢你
Thank you.
帮我跟莎拉
Helping me with Sara,
我知道  这样做不容易
I know that that... can't be easy.
帮两个我在乎的人吗
Helping two people I care about?
没有比这更容易的事了
There's nothing easier.
我是来带莎拉去吃饭的
I came by to take Sara to dinner.
你想一起去吃吗
Would you care to join?
我很想去  但是得先去见个老朋友
I'd love to, but I need to go see an old friend.
好吧
OK.
你好  奥利弗
Hello, Oliver.
你好  阿曼达
Hello, Amanda.
还生我的气吗
Still mad at me?
算你走运  你不在我的名单之上了
Lucky for you, You've been pushed down that list.
真的吗  跟我相比你更加想杀的人是谁
Really? Who do you want to kill more than me?
斯莱德·威尔逊还活着
Slade Wilson is alive.
你把他杀了
You killed him.
不可能还活着的
It's not possible.
只要跟斯莱德有关  一切皆有可能
Everything is possible where Slade is concerned.
我需要你帮我找到他
And I need your help to find him.
-我可能有线索  -什么线索
- I might have something. - What?
我们一直追踪的一个人  是个雇佣兵
There's a new player we've been tracking-- mercenary.
他所到之处尸体遍地
He's left a trail of bodies
从澳门到伊斯坦布尔再到里斯本
from Macau to Istanbul to Lisbon.
最后到了星城
A trail that leads right here to Starling.
我们一直叫他丧钟
We've been calling him Deathstroke.